 const msword_quiz =  [
      {
        "question": "1.     How many different positions can you set for drop cap ?",
        "option1" : "a)   1",
        "option2" : "b)   2",
        "option3" : "c)   4",
        "option4" : "d)   6",
        "answer"  : "b)   2"
      },
      {
        "question": "2.     How many ways you can save a document ?",
        "option1" : "a)   3",
        "option2" : "b)   4",
        "option3" : "c)   5",
        "option4" : "d)   6",
        "answer"  : "a)   3"
      },
      {
        "question": "3.     Single spacing in MS Word document causes - point line spacing ?",
        "option1" : "a)   10",
        "option2" : "b)   12",
        "option3" : "c)   14",
        "option4" : "d)   16",
        "answer"  : "b)   12"
      },
      {
        "question": "4.     What is the default number of lines to drop for drop cap ?",
        "option1" : "a)   3",
        "option2" : "b)   10",
        "option3" : "c)   15",
        "option4" : "d)   20",
        "answer"  : "a)   3"
      },
      {
        "question": "5.     What is the maximum number of lines you can set for a drop cap ?",
        "option1" : "a)   3",
        "option2" : "b)   10",
        "option3" : "c)   15",
        "option4" : "d)   20",
        "answer"  : "b)   10"
      },
      {
        "question": "6.     How many column can you insert in a word document in maximum ?",
        "option1" : "a)   35",
        "option2" : "b)   45",
        "option3" : "c)   55",
        "option4" : "d)   65",
        "answer"  : "b)   45"
      },
      {
        "question": "7.     In a document, What is the maximum number of columns that can be inserted in MS-Word Table ?",
        "option1" : "a)   35",
        "option2" : "b)   15",
        "option3" : "c)   63",
        "option4" : "d)   65",
        "answer"  : "c)   63"
      },
      {
        "question": "8.     What is the maximum scale percentage available in scale drop down box ?",
        "option1" : "a)   500",
        "option2" : "b)   200",
        "option3" : "c)   100",
        "option4" : "d)   90",
        "answer"  : "b)   200"
      },
      {
        "question": "9.     What is the maximum font size you can apply for any character ?",
        "option1" : "a)   163",
        "option2" : "b)   1638",
        "option3" : "c)   16038",
        "option4" : "d)   None of these",
        "answer"  : "b)   1638"
      },
      {
        "question": "10.     Word by default, places a tab step at every_mark on the ruler ?",
        "option1" : 'a)   2.5"',
        "option2" : 'b)   .5"',
        "option3" : 'c)   .75"',
        "option4" : 'd)   .1"',
        "answer"  : 'b)   .5"'
      },
      {
        "question": "11.     What is the default file extension for all word documents ?",
        "option1" : "a)   txt",
        "option2" : "b)   word",
        "option3" : "c)   docs",
        "option4" : "d)   docx",
        "answer"  : "d)   docx"
      },
      {
        "question": "12.     The file type_indicates the file is a word document ?",
        "option1" : "a)   .msw",
        "option2" : "b)   .wor",
        "option3" : "c)   .wrd",
        "option4" : "d)   .doc",
        "answer"  : "d)   .doc"
      },
      {
        "question": "13.     How much space in minimum must be provided between columns ?",
        "option1" : 'a)   0"',
        "option2" : 'b)   0.5"',
        "option3" : 'c)   1"',
        "option4" : 'd)   1.5"',
        "answer"  : 'a)   0"'
      },
      {
        "question": "14.     What is the smallest width of column ?",
        "option1" : 'a)   0"',
        "option2" : 'b)   0.5"',
        "option3" : 'c)   1"',
        "option4" : 'd)   1.5"',
        "answer"  : 'd)   1.5"'
      },
      {
        "question": "15.     By default, your document print with ?",
        "option1" : "a)   1 inch top and bottom margins",
        "option2" : "b)   A portrait orientation",
        "option3" : "c)   1.25 inches left and right margins",
        "option4" : "d)   All of the above",
        "answer"  : "b)   A portrait orientation"
      },
      {
        "question": "16.     Word is present to use standard 8.5 by 11 inch paper with_margins ?",
        "option1" : "a)   1 inch left, right, top and bottom",
        "option2" : "b)   1.25 inch left, right top and bottom",
        "option3" : "c)   1.25 inch left and right margins and depend button",
        "option4" : "d)   1 inch left and right margins and 1.25 inch top and bottom",
        "answer"  : "c)   1.25 inch left and right margins and depend button"
      },
      {
        "question": "17.     What is the default left margin in word 2003 document ?",
        "option1" : 'a)   1"',
        "option2" : 'b)   1.25"',
        "option3" : 'c)   1.5"',
        "option4" : 'd)   2"',
        "answer"  : 'b)   1.25"(31.7mm)'
      },
      {
        "question": "18.     What is the smallest and largest font size available in font size tool on formatting toolbar ?",
        "option1" : "a)   8 and 72",
        "option2" : "b)   8 and 64",
        "option3" : "c)   12 and 72",
        "option4" : "d)   None of above",
        "answer"  : "a)   8 and 72"
      },
      {
        "question": "19.     What is the default font size of a new word document based on normal template in word 2003 ?",
        "option1" : "a)   10pt",
        "option2" : "b)   12pt",
        "option3" : "c)   14pt",
        "option4" : "d)   None of above",
        "answer"  : "b)   12pt"
      },
      {
        "question": "20.     The minimum number of rows and columns in MS-Word document is ?",
        "option1" : "a)   1 and 1",
        "option2" : "b)   2 and 1",
        "option3" : "c)   2 and 2",
        "option4" : "d)   None of above",
        "answer"  : "a)   1 and 1"
      },
      {
        "question": "21.     In mail merge operation which of the following might represent the main document ?",
        "option1" : "a)   A scale brochure",
        "option2" : "b)   A form letter",
        "option3" : "c)   A database of Names and Addresses",
        "option4" : "d)   None of above",
        "answer"  : "a)   A scale brochure"
      },
      {
        "question": "22.     Pressing F8 key for three times select ?",
        "option1" : "a)   A word",
        "option2" : "b)   A sentense",
        "option3" : "c)   A paragraph",
        "option4" : "d)   entire document",
        "answer"  : "b)   A sentense"
      },
      {
        "question": "22.     What do you call a collection of character and paragraph formatting commands ?",
        "option1" : "a)   A style",
        "option2" : "b)   A template",
        "option3" : "c)   A style",
        "option4" : "d)   A boilerplate",
        "answer"  : "a)   A style"
      },
      {
        "question": "23.     What is document outline view ?",
        "option1" : "a)   A preview in a full screen",
        "option2" : "b)   A preview with margins",
        "option3" : "c)   A view with a margins and gutter",
        "option4" : "d)   A view with a structure of heading at various levels",
        "answer"  : "d)   A view with a structure of heading of various levels"
      },
      {
        "question": "24.     Ctrl+Z ?",
        "option1" : "a)   Undo the last action",
        "option2" : "b)   Redo the last action",
        "option3" : "c)   Add the new page",
        "option4" : "d)   Paste the contents clipboard",
        "answer"  : "a)   Undo the last action"
      },
      {
        "question": "25.     The ____ in the resume wizard dialog box indicates the wizard is ready to create the document ?",
        "option1" : "a)   Start panel",
        "option2" : "b)   Address panel",
        "option3" : "c)   Add/Sort Heading panel",
        "option4" : "d)   Finish panel",
        "answer"  : "d)   Finish panel"
      },
      {
        "question": "26.     What does Ctrl + = key effect ?",
        "option1" : "a)   Superscript",
        "option2" : "b)   Subscript",
        "option3" : "c)   All caps",
        "option4" : "d)   Shadow",
        "answer"  : "b)   Subscript"
      },
      {
        "question": "27.     The word wrap feature ?",
        "option1" : "a)   Automatically move text to the next line when necessary",
        "option2" : "b)   Appears at the bottom of the document",
        "option3" : "c)   All you to type over text",
        "option4" : "d)   It is the short horizontal line",
        "answer"  : "a)   Automatically move text to the next line when necessary"
      },
      {
        "question": "28.     How can you make the selected character superscriptd ?",
        "option1" : "a)   Ctrl + =",
        "option2" : "b)   Ctrl + Shift + =",
        "option3" : "c)   Alt + Ctrl + shift + =",
        "option4" : "d)   None of Above",
        "answer"  : "b)   Ctrl + Shift + ="
      },
      {
        "question": "29.     When typing in a word field manually, what must you press to insert the code's braces ?",
        "option1" : "a)   Ctrl + F6",
        "option2" : "b)   Ctrl + F9",
        "option3" : "c)   Alt + F9",
        "option4" : "d)   Shift + F12",
        "answer"  : "b)   Ctrl + F9"
      },
      {
        "question": "30.     What is the shortcut key to open the open dialog box ?",
        "option1" : "a)   F12",
        "option2" : "b)   Shift + F12",
        "option3" : "c)   Alt + F12",
        "option4" : "d)   Ctrl + F12",
        "answer"  : "d)   Ctrl + F12"
      },
      {
        "question": "31.     What is the shortcut key to split a table ?",
        "option1" : "a)   Ctrl + Alt + Enter",
        "option2" : "b)   Ctrl + Shift + Enter",
        "option3" : "c)   Alt + Shift + Enter",
        "option4" : "d)   Alt + Space + Enter",
        "answer"  : "b)   Ctrl + Shift + Enter"
      },
      {
        "question": "32.     Which key is use to increase left indent ?",
        "option1" : "a)   Ctrl + i",
        "option2" : "b)   Ctrl + m",
        "option3" : "c)   Alt + i",
        "option4" : "d)   F10",
        "answer"  : "b)   Ctrl + m"
      },
      {
        "question": "33.     When the same word is used in multiple locatons or a word is used to that was not quite appropriate, a thesaurus can used to look up an ___ or a word similar in meaning ?",
        "option1" : "a)   Synonym",
        "option2" : "b)   Homonym",
        "option3" : "c)   Antonym",
        "option4" : "d)   Metronym",
        "answer"  : "a)   Synonym"
      },
      {
        "question": "34.     How many different documents you can open at one time ?",
        "option1" : "a)   No more than three",
        "option2" : "b)   Only one",
        "option3" : "c)   As many as your computer memory will hold",
        "option4" : "d)   As many as your taskbar can display",
        "answer"  : "c)   As many as your computer memory will hold."
      },
      {
        "question": "35.     Which of the following is the second step in creating a macro ?",
        "option1" : "a)   Start recording",
        "option2" : "b)   Using your mouse or keyboard, perform that task you want to automate",
        "option3" : "c)   Assign a keyboard shortcut to the macro ",
        "option4" : "d)   Give the macro a name",
        "answer"  : "d)   Give the macro a name"
      },
      {
        "question": "36.      When assigning a shortcut key to a symbol, you should always try to select a key or key combination that is :",
        "option1" : "a)   Unassigned",
        "option2" : "b)   Located on the ten key pad selection of your keyboard",
        "option3" : "c)   Assigned to another task",
        "option4" : "d)   None of the above",
        "answer"  : "a)   Unassigned"
      },
      {
        "question": "37.     Which feature is used to replace straight quotes with smart quotes as yuou typw ?",
        "option1" : "a)   Fixed column width",
        "option2" : "b)   Autofit to contents",
        "option3" : "c)   Autofit to windows",
        "option4" : "d)   Autofit to column",
        "answer"  : "d)   Autofit to column."
      },
      {
        "question": "38.     When you click on file menu in word 2010, it open  ?",
        "option1" : "a)   File menu",
        "option2" : "b)   File command",
        "option3" : "c)   Backstage view",
        "option4" : "d)   File Ribbon",
        "answer"  : "c)   Backstage view"
      },
      {
        "question": "39.     Tab stop position cannot be  ?",
        "option1" : "a)   No more than three",
        "option2" : "b)   Only one",
        "option3" : "c)   As many as your computer memory will hold",
        "option4" : "d)   As many as your taskbar can display",
        "answer"  : "c)   As many as your computer memory will hold."
      },
      {
        "question": "40.     Ctrl + B ?",
        "option1" : "a)   Search the selected text",
        "option2" : "b)   Paste the selected text",
        "option3" : "c)   Bold the selected text",
        "option4" : "d)   Open the specified file",
        "answer"  : "c)   Bold the selected text"
      },
    ];

  export default msword_quiz;